Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Women's Rights Serials TAM.751
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Women's Rights Serials
1907-2010
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
National Organization for Women
International Socialists (U.S.)
National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League
TAM.751
26.94 Linear Feet in 11 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, 17 flat boxes, and 6 folders in a shared manuscript box
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Women's Rights Serials groups 408 titles broadly relating to women's rights, published between 1907 and 2010, originally received by the Tamiment Library through subscriptions, donations, and as part of archival collections. The majority of the collection consists of incomplete runs of newspapers, newsletters, magazines, and bulletins, with a smaller quantity of one-off reports and catalogs, published by women's rights organizations, encompassing activist networks, research bodies, academic institutions, government agencies, and nonprofits. Many periodicals were created during the height of the women's rights movement in the 1970s and 1980s, and document the early discourse around women's liberation. At a granular level, the serials document the discussions surrounding gender equality, workplace discrimination, sexuality, reproductive rights, and female solidarity.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Women's Rights Serials groups 408 titles broadly relating to women's rights, published between 1907 and 2010, originally received by the Tamiment Library through subscriptions, donations, and as part of archival collections. The majority of the collection consists of incomplete runs of newspapers, newsletters, magazines, and bulletins, with a smaller quantity of one-off reports and catalogs, published by women's rights organizations, encompassing activist networks, research bodies, academic institutions, government agencies, and nonprofits. A significant quantity of the collection dates from the 1970s and 1980s, when interest in women's rights surged, chronicling early mainstream discourse around the women's liberation movement. The serials provide contemporaneous coverage of a wide range of issues of concern to women and feminist groups between the 1970s and early 2000s, broadly addressing gender equality, workplace discrimination, sexuality, reproductive rights, and female solidarity.
Among the topics addressed in the serials are equal pay, gender discrimination in employment, activism for workplace and organizational justice, sexual harassment, mental health, abortion and reproductive health, sexual assault, international solidarity, and childrearing and motherhood. A small number of publications dating from the early 20th century also document women's suffrage movements in the United States and Great Britain. There are also several publications addressing male sexuality and gender identity. These publications largely reflect solidarity with the women's liberation movement, and explore social constructions of masculinity.
Many periodicals come from independent regional publishers in the United States, while a small amount were produced by international publishers in Canada, Europe, China, Australia, Pakistan, and Cuba. The National Organization for Women (NOW) is among the most prominently featured publishers, with publications from the organization's national body as well as regional chapters. No complete runs of publications are contained herein, and generally only a handful of issues of each publication are held.
Arrangement
Periodicals in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to the women's rights movement drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of certain original materials, researchers may be required to consult microfilm copies, preservation photocopies, or digital images of material in this collection.
Custodial History
In December 2025, 9 copies of the National NOW Times; 24 copies of NOW NYC News; 31 copies of NOW News; a copy of Do It Now; a copy of Notes from the First Year: New York Radical Women; a copy of Notes from the Third Year: Women's Liberation; 7 copies of Now Acts; 2 copies of the Political Times; a copy of WomaNews; 2 copies NOW-NYS Action Report; 7 copies of the National Task Force on Marriage, Divorce, and Family Relations newsletter; and 22 copies of the Marriage, Divorce, and the Family Newsletter were removed from the National Organization for Women: New York City Chapter Records (TAM 106) and added to TAM 751.
Women's rights -- United States -- 20th century; Women's rights -- New York (State) -- New York.; Feminism -- United States -- History -- 20th century.; Women's health services -- Political aspects -- United States.; Reproductive rights -- United States; Sex discrimination in employment.; Organizational justice.
- ยง218-Zeitung: Brot et Rosen, Berlin, Germany, circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 1)
- $pread Magazine: Spread Magazine, New York, NY, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- A Woman's Work: Barnard College / Arlene van Breems, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Academic Feminists and the Women's Movement: Ain't I A Woman?/AIAW Collective, Iowa City, IA, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Activists Panels: 1970 Socialist Activists and Educational Conference Reports: Socialist Activists and Educational Conference (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Afterbirth: Libertarian Book Club, Decatur, GA, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Aikanainen Kvinnotid: Utgivare-Julkaisija, Helsinki, Finland, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Ain't I A Woman: AIAW Collective, Iowa City, IA, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2-3, Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 13)
- Alliance Against Women's Oppression: Alliance Against Women's Oppression, San Francisco, CA, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Alternative Vision: University of California, San Diego, La Jolla, CA, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Alternatives to Fear: Alternatives to fear, Seattle, WA, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Alternatives to Fear: Alternatives to Fear and King County Women's Program, Seattle, WA, circa 1970s (Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 19)
- Annual Report: National-American Woman Suffrage Association, Warren, OH, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- As One! For Equality, For Happiness, For Peace: World Congress of Women: Reports, Speeches (Extracts), Documents: Women's International Democratic Federation, Berlin, Germany, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Aurat: Aurat, Lahore, Pakistan, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Awake & Move: Philadelphia Women's Liberation Center, Penllyn, PA, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Barnard Bulletin: Barnard College, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Berkeley/Oakland Women's Union Newsletter: Berkeley/Oakland Women's Union, Berkeley, CA, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Between Our Selves: Between Our Selves, Washington, DC, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Between Our Selves: Women of Color Newspaper: Between Our Selves, Washington, DC, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Blast: OpenRoad, Vancouver, Canada, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Body Politic: Body Politic Inc., New York, NY, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bread and Roses: Bread and Roses, Chicago, IL, circa 1970s (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Bridges: Bridges Association, Eugene, OR, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Bridges: New Jewish Agenda, Inc., Seattle, WA, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Now Newsletter: Brooklyn NOW, Brooklyn, NY, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Broomstick: Broomstick, San Francisco, CA, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Brother: Male Liberation Newspaper: Brother Collective, Berkeley, CA, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 9, Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 12)
- Brother Newsletter: Brother Collective, Berkeley, CA, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Brother: a Forum for Men Against Sexism: Brother Collective, Berkeley, CA, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- California Women's Health Network Newsletter: California Women's Health Network, San Francisco, CA, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Calling All Women: Suffragette Fellowship, Leicester, England, 1966-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Camping Women Trails: Camping Women, Sacramento, CA, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Center Quarterly: Center for Women's Studies and Services, San Diego, CA, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Change: A Working Woman's Newspaper: Change, San Francisco, CA, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Changing Experience of Women: Open University Press, Milton Keynes, England, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Changing Men: Feminist Men's Publications, Inc., Madison, WI, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Changing Woman: Changing Woman, Inc., Portland, OR, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Choice: Washington State Naral, Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Clearinghouse for Feminist Media: Clearinghouse for Feminist Media, Ancaster, Ontario, Canada, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center Women's Group: Columbia University, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Common Woman: Common Woman Collective, Berkeley, CA, circa 1970s (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Due to the fragile condition of this material, access may be supervised or restricted.
- Common Woman: Common Woman Collective, Berkeley, CA, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Commonwoman: Commonwoman, Inc., Winooski, VT, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Coyote Howls: Loose Women's Organization, San Francisco, CA, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 15, Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 14)
- CWLU News: Chicago Women's Liberation Committee, Chicago, IL, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Daily Woman: Daily Woman Corp., Albany, NY, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- De Maatschappelijke Ontwikkeling en de Bevrijding der Vrouw: W.L. & J. Brusse, Rotterdam, Netherlands, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Detroit Women's Press: Detroit Women's Press, Detroit, MI, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Distaff: Distaff / Feminist Forum, New Orleans, LA, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Do It NOW: National Organization for Women, Chicago, IL, 1971-1972, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Do It NOW: National Organization for Women / National NOW Action Center, Washington, D.C., 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2, Box 28, Folder 15)
- Do It NOW: National Organization of Women, Washington, DC, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Double-F: A Magazine of Efferminism: Templar Press, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Downtown Women's News: Women Organized for Employment, San Francisco, CA, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Emma: Zeitschrift fรผr Frauen von Frauen: Emma-Frauenverl, Koln, Germany, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Equal Time: a Women's Newspaper: Equal Time, Wichita, KS, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Equal Times: Women for Change Center / Women's Center of Dallas, Dallas, TX, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 5, Box 25, Folder 6)
- Equality In Minnesota: National Organization for Women, Saint Paul, MN, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Equinox: Equinox Enterprises, Inc., Newton, MA, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Everywoman: Everywoman Newspaper, Venice, CA, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Everywoman: Everywoman Newspaper, Los Angeles, CA, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Examiner: A Newsletter of the Feminist Women's Health Center: Feminist Women's Health Center, Tallahassee, FL, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Executive Woman: Sandra Brown Advertising, New York, NY, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Feelings: Feelings, Brooklyn, NY, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Female State: A Journal of Female Liberation: Journal of Female Liberation, Somerville, MA, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Feminist: Feminist, Berkeley, CA, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Feminist Newsservice Newsletter: Feminist Newsservice of the United States, Denver, CO, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Feminist Party News: Feminist Party / Irene Davall, New York, NY, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15, Box 25, Folder 7)
- Feminist Times: Feminist Times Associates, New York, NY, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Feminist Voice: Feminist Voice Collective, Chicago, IL, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- First Revolution: A Journal of Female Liberation: Journal of Female Liberation, Cambridge, MA, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Food We Eat: Berkeley Women's Health Collective Nutrition Committee, Berkeley, CA, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fourth World: Fourth World Publications, Oakland, CA, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Frauenzeitung: Frauengruppe Mannheim, Mannheim, Germany, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Freedom from Rape: Women's Crisis Center of Ann Arbor, Ann Arbor, MI, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Full Moon: Valley Women's Center, Amherst, MA, circa 1970s (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Generations: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, Lexington, KY, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Gibbous Rising: Feminist News Collective, Sacramento, CA, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Gloria Steinem and the CIA: Redstockings of the Women's Liberation Movement, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Hand That Rocks the Rock: Slippery Rock Women' Liberation, Slippery Rock, PA, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Her-self: Her-self, Inc., Ann Arbor, MI, 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Heresies: A Feminist Publication on Art & Politics: Heresies Collective, Inc., New York, NY, 1980, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Home Industries of Women in London: Women's Industrial Council, London, England, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Hysteria: Hysteria Newspaper, Boston, MA, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Interim: Journalism Department, Boston University School of Public Communication, Boston, MA, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- International Women's Day 1970: Women's Caucus of Youth Against War & Fascism, New York, NY (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Intertrend Report: Intertrend Communications, Brooklyn, NY, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- It Ain't Me Babe: Women's Liberation Basement Press Collective, Berkeley, CA, 1970-1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- It Is Not My Baby: Berkeley Women's Liberation, Berkeley, CA, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- IVe Session du Comite Executif: Federation Democratique Internationale des Femmes, Paris, France, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- IVth Congress of Women's International Democratic Federation: Secretariat of the Women's International Democratic Federation, Berlin, Germany, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Jane Doe: Women's Peaceworker Committee of the Women's Center / Women's Encampment for a Future of Peace and Justice, Binghamton, NY, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 4, Box 25, Folder 10)
- Japan Feminist: Japan Feminist / Ikuko Atsumi, Tokyo, Japan, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Jetzt reden wir: Jetzt reden Wir, Munich, Germany, circa 1970s (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Journey Womyn: The Catalyst: A Chicago Womyn's Paper:, Chicago, IL, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Kinesis: Vancouver Status of Women, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1976-1977, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
- Kings County Rape Relief Ramblings: KCRR, Renton, WA, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- La Via Femminile: Rivista Trimestrale, Rome, Italy, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Labyrinth: Philadelphia Women's Newspaper, Philadelphia, PA, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Le Torchon Brule: Marie Dedieu, Paris, France, circa 1970s (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Les Cahiers Feministes:, Paris, France, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Les Tetes de Pioche: Les Tetes de Pioche, Motreal, Quebec, Canada, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Letter Series: New York State Woman Suffrage Party, New York, NY, circa 1910s (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Lewisham's Wageless Women: The Invisible Unemployed: Lewisham Women and Employment Project, London, England, circa 1980s (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Liberation of Women: Sexual Repression and the Family: New England Free Press, Boston, MA, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Libertad (NY-Mares): Mujeres an Accion Pro Reivindicaciones Economicas y Sociales, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Longest Revolution: Center for Women's Studies and Services, San Diego, CA, 1976-1977, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Longest Revolution: Center for Women's Studies and Services / Collective of the Center for Women's Studies & Services, San Diego, CA, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- M.: Gentle Men for Gender Justice: University YMCA Communist Center, Madison, WI, 1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Madre: Madre, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Madre: Women's Peace Network, Inc., New York, NY, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Madre Speaks: Madre, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Madre Speaks: Women's Peace Network, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Madre: We Dream Our Highest Dreams: Women's Peace Network, New York, NY, 1989-1991 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Majority Report: Majority Report / Women's Strike Coalition, New York, NY, 1971-1978 (Box 15, Folder 1-5, Box 25, Folder 14)
- Majority Report: Majority Report / Women's Strike Coalition, Jamaica, NY, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Make a Change: Batterers' Project, Seattle, WA, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Margaret Sanger Papers Project Newsletter: Department of History, New York University, New York, NY, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Marin Women's Newsletter: Marin Women's Newsletter, San Rafael, CA, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 12, Box 25, Folder 15-16)
- Mass. Childbearing Rights Alliance Newsletter: Mass. Childbering Rights Alliance, Boston, MA, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Matriarchist: Foundation for Matriarchy, Brooklyn, NY, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Me Jane: MeJane Collective, Sydney, Australia, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Memo: League of Women Voters, Washington, DC, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Men Sharing: Men Sharing, Boston, MA, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Men's Pages: Freefall, Evanston, IL, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Metropolitan New York: Project Equality, Brooklyn, NY, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Momma: Momma, Venice, CA, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Momma: Momma, Venice, CA, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Motherlode: San Francisco Women's Liberation, San Francisco, CA, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Mountain Moving Day: n.p., Carbondale, IL, circa 1970s (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Muchacha: Muchacha, Cuba, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Mushroom Effect: Mushroom Effect, Albany, CA, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Mushroom Effect: Mushroom Effect, Albany, CA, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- MWPC Newsletter: Manhattan Women's Political Caucus, New York, NY, 1972-1973, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 19, Box 25, Folder 18)
- N.O.W. Compliance and Enforcement Task Force: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- National Newsletter: Feminist Writers' Guild, Berkeley, CA, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- National NOW - Marriage and Divorce Committee Newsletter: New York, NY, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 22, Box Shared Tamiment 205, Folder 6)
- National NOW - Marriage, Divorce, and the Family Newsletter: New York, NY, 1974-1977 (Box Shared Tamiment 205, Folder 7)
- National NOW Newsletter: Education Task Force, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- National NOW Times: National Organization For Women, Washington, DC, 1978, 1981, 1985, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 12, Box 28, Folder 1-2)
- NCCWO Bulletin: National Committee to Combat Women's Oppression, Columbus, OH, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Neighborhood Woman: National Congress of Neighborhood Women, Brooklyn, NY, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Neighborhood Women: National Congress of Neighborhood Women, Brooklyn, NY, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Network: English Collective of Prostitutes, London, England, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- New Carolina Woman: New Carolina Woman, Fayetteville, NC, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- New Directions for Women: New Directions for Women, Inc., Englewood, NJ, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- New Space: New Time: New Space: New Time, Landenberg, PA, circa 1970s (Box 14, Folder 16)
- New Women's Times: New Women's Times, Rochester, NY, 1976-1979 (Box 16, Folder 1-4, Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 11)
- New York Feminist Manhattan Tribune: Manhattan Tribune, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- New York Radical Feminists Newsletter: New York Radical Feminists, New York, NY, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- New York Radical Women Calendar: NYC Radical Women, Harlem, NY, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- New York Woman: National Organization for Women New York Chapter, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- New York Women's Week: Activa Publications, Ltd., New York, NY, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- New's letter: Nontraditional Employment for Women, New York, NY, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- News: Women's Occupational Health Resource Center, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- News from the National Women's Conference Committee: Continuing Committee of the International Women's Year, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- News Letter: n.p., Seattle, WA, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Newsletter: International Women's Tribune Center, Inc., New York, NY, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Newsletter: National Abortion Rights Action League, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Newsletter: National Organization for Women / National Task Force - Marriage, Divorce and Family Relations, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 33, Box 26, Folder 1)
- Newsletter: NOW Task Force on Older Women, Oakland, CA, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Newsletter: Women's Law Center, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Newsletter: Working Women Organization, Lahore Cantt, Pakistan, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Newsletter: Women's History, Literature, & Art: Her Own Words, Madison, WI, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Newsletter WOAR: Women Organized Against Rape, Philadelphia, PA, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Newsnotes: Feminist Press, Old Westbury, NY, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Newsnotes: Feminist Press, Old Westbury, NY, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Non-traditional employment for women newsletter: Non-Traditional Employment for Women, New York, NY, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Notes from EMILY: Emily's List, Washington, DC, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Notes from the First Year: New York Radical Women, New York, NY, 1968 (Box Shared Tamiment 205, Folder 8)
- Notes from the Second Year: Radical Feminism, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5, Box 26, Folder 3)
- Notes from the Third Year: Women's Liberation, New York, NY, 1971 (Box Shared Tamiment 205, Folder 9)
- NOW Acts: National Organization for Women, Chicago, IL, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 7, Box 26, Folder 4, Box Shared Tamiment 205, Folder 10)
- NOW Compliance Newsletter: National Organization for Women - Central New Jersey Chapter, Princeton, NJ, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- NOW is the time: Thurston County Chapter of the National Organization for Women, Olympia, WA, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- NOW New York Chapter News: National Organization for Women New York Chapter, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NOW New York Chapter News: National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter, New York, NY, 1971, 1975-1977, 1987-1992, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9, Box 28, Folder 3-6)
- NOW New York State: National Organization for Women in New York, Newark, NY, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10, Box 26, Folder 6)
- Now News: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1994, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Now News: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1993, 1998-2003, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 1, Box 28, Folder 7-11)
- Now News- Mixed Chapters: National Organization for Women, New York, NY, 1994, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 7-8)